Imogen Cunningham
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Imogen Cunningham papers
1903-1991
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Imogen Cunningham
5.5 linear feet
The papers of photographer and teacher Imogen Cunningham, date from 1903 to 1991. The collection measures 5.5 feet of material, including correspondence, business and financial records, writings, printed matter, and photographs, and provides a good overview of Cunningham's life and career.
Biographical Note
Born in Portland, Oregon on April 12, 1883, Cunningham's family moved to Seattle in 1889. Inspired by Gertrude Kasebier's work, she purchased her first camera in 1901. After studying chemistry and botany at the University of Washington, she worked for the Edward S. Curtis Studio, Seattle, from 1907 to 1909. Receiving a scholarship, Cunningham studied for a year at the Technische Hochschule, Dresden.
Upon her return to Seattle in 1910, she opened a studio and had the first major exhibition of her work at the Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences in 1912.
In 1915, Cunningham married printmaker Roi Partridge and gave birth to her first son, Gryffyd. Two years later, her family moved to California, where she gave birth to twin sons, Padraic and Rondal. In 1920, the family moved to Oakland, where her husband taught at Mills College. During the 1920s, she exhibited her art work and began photographing plant forms.
Along with Ansel Adams, John Paul Edwards, Sonya Noskowiak, Henry Swift, Willard Van Dyke, and Edward Weston, Cunningham formed the f/64 Group, a society of purist photographers in 1932. During the same year she began working for Vanity Fair and other magazines and began a career as a portrait photographer, including Martha Graham, Cary Grant, Morris Graves, Alfred Stieglitz, and Spencer Tracy as her subjects. She divorced her husband in 1934.
In 1947, Cunningham established a studio in her San Francisco home, and continued to exhibit extensively until her death on June 24, 1976.
Scope and Content Note
The papers of photographer and teacher Imogen Cunningham, date from 1903 to 1991. The collection measures 5.5 feet of material, including correspondence, business and financial records, writings, printed matter, and photographs, and provides a good overview of Cunningham's life and career. 3.6 linear feet of correspondence comprise the bulk of the collection.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into ten series according to material type:
Series 1: Biographical Material, 1907-1981, undated (box 1; 4 folders)
Series 2: Correspondence, 1909-1991, undated (boxes 1-4; 3.6 linear feet)
Series 3: Personal Business Records, 1944-1976 (box 4; 15 folders)
Series 4: Notes, 1959-1968 (box 4; 10 folders)
Series 5: Teaching Files, 1964-1971 (box 5; 4 folders)
Series 6: Writings, circa 1910-1976 (box 5; 21 folders)
Series 7: Interview Transcripts, 1951, undated (box 5; 2 folders)
Series 8: Printed Material, 1903-1991 (boxes 5-7; 1.2 linear feet)
Series 9: Photographs, 1916-1976 (box 7; 12 folders)
Series 10: Oversized Material, 1947-1948, 1967, undated
Appendix: List of Notable Correspondents
The following provides a list of notable correspondents from Series 2: Correspondence, showing dates of correspondence. Entries marked with an asterisk (*) indicate letters written by Imogen Cunningham.
Al: Apr 21, 1969*
Al and Phil: Jul 07, 1968*; Jan 02, 1969*; Nov 29, 1969*
Alfred: Dec 28, 1968*; Jul 12, 1969*
Arvilla: Feb 22, 1953
Barbara and Dave: Jul 09, 1968*; May 19, 1971*
Becky: undated
Bess: Mar 19, 1969*
Betsey: Dec 05, 1954*
Betty: Nov 17, 1970*
Beverley: Jan 24, 1966*
Bill: May 08, 1973*
Boris: Aug 28, 1957*
Caroline: Apr 05, 1971*; Jun 28, 1971
Cathy: Jan 06, 1969*
Charis: May 10, 1976
David and Laura: Dec 28, 1974*
Dick: May 29, 1970*; Oct 16, 1970
Dick and Perry: Apr 05, 1975*
Dory and Paul: Sep 14, 1964*
Ed: Nov 19, 1968*; Mar 12, 1969*
Ellen: Dec 16, 1965*; Oct 30, 1974*
Elsa and Joe: undated
Ethel and Willard: Dec 01, 1953*
Evelyn: May 02, 1970
Florence: Mar 10, 1969
Frances: undated; Jul 12, 1966*
Frank: May 15, 1965*
Gael: Sep 02, 1971*
Helen: May 08, 1963*; Jun 02, 1965*; Dec 31, 1973*
Jan: Aug 03, 1974*
Jane and Steve: Jul 07, 1974*
Jean: Jan 06, 1969*; mentioned in letter dated Feb 07, 1969*
Jei?: May 03, 1961
Jim: May 29, 1974
John: Dec 25, 1971*; May 05, 1974
Jose: Jul 06, 1968*
Lato: Feb 17, 1965
Lilli ann: Nov 02, 1971*
Liz: Jan 08, 1965*
Liz and Louis: Jan 12, 1972*
Liz and Peter: Dec 1951
Maggie: Jan 04, 1971
Margaret: Sep 06, 1964*; Feb 28, 1966*; Mar 04, 1966; Nov 12, 1968*; Feb 11, 1972*; Sep 12, 1973*
Mary: Apr 04, 1967*; Apr 15, 1967; Jun 19, 1967*; Nov 25, 1969; Apr 12, 1970; Aug 31, 1970*; Nov 08, 1970*; Apr 23, 1974; Jan 31, 1976
Mia: Oct 08, 1958*
Midge: Jun 14, 1967*
Mildred: Nov 12, 1965
Nancy: Oct 22, 1966*; Apr 03, 1971*
Neil: Feb 18, 1961*: Nov 17, 1960*; Apr 27, 1962*
Otto and Virika?: Jun 18, 1976
Pat (Goucher College): undated; May 15, 1956; Feb 06, 1964*
Patience: Nov 24, 1959*
Paul: Jun 06, 1970
Peg: Feb 15, 1966
Peggy: Aug 30, 1970*
Phil: Oct 07, 1961
Ruth: Mar 20, 1955*
Ruth (jewelry maker): Aug 10, 1967
Samuel: Aug 12, 1968*
Thur: Dec 15, 1956
Tina (Cunningham relative): Feb 08, 1974; Feb 19, 1974*
Trevor, Thomas, Allen and Stan: Apr 09, 1970*; Mar 28, 1974*
Trisha: [Dec 1973]
831 Photographic Gallery: Jan 15, 1971; Jan 26, 1971*; Apr 10, 1971; Apr 17, 1971*; Apr 11, 1972; May 02, 1972; May 22, 1972*; Jun 07, 1972*; Jul 05, 1972; Jul 11, 1972*; Feb 21, 1974; Mar 06, 1974*
Aalto, Alvar: Jun 08, 1962; Jun 16, 1962*; Jul 02, 1962; Aug 03, 1963*; Sep 9, 1963
Adams, Ansel and Virginia: mentioned in [undated] letter from Cunningham to an unidentified correspondent; undated; Mar 01, 1941; Aug 03, 1949; Mar 28, 1951; Apr 02, 1951 (letter from Minor White); Aug 04, 1952; Jan 10, 1963; Apr 04, 1963; Dec 22, 1963; Jan 03, 1964; Jan 22, 1964*; Jan 23, 1964; Jan 28, 1964*; Feb 07, 1964; Feb 10, 1964*; Feb 12, 1964; Mar 09, 1964*; Mar 18, 1964*; Mar 22, 1964; Mar 26, 1964; Mar 28, 1964*; Apr 09, 1964*; May 21, 1964; Sep 17, 1964*; Sep 18, 1964; Dec 09, 1964; Feb 12, 1965; Jan 12, 1966; Jan 24, 1967; [Apr 12, 1966]; Feb 09, 1967*; Feb 13, 1967; May 22, 1967; May 24, 1967; May 25, 1967; Jun 14, 1967; Aug 14, 1967*; May 05, 1968; Jun 10, 1968*; Jun 14, 1968; Jan 25, 1969; Mar 10, 1969; Jun 04, 1969; Jul 16, 1969*; Jul 19, 1969; Aug 12, 1969*; Aug 13, 1969; Aug 21, 1969*; Dec 09, 1969*; Feb 06, 1970*; Feb 11, 1970; Apr 10, 1970; Jun 15, 1970*; Jul 05, 1970*; Jul 12, 1970; Sep 15, 1970; Dec 14, 1970; Feb 15, 1971; Apr 23, 1971*; Aug 05, 1971; Mar 26, 1972*; Aug 18, 1972; Apr 11, 1973; Jun 30, 1973*; Jul 02, 1973; Dec 13, 1973*; Dec 16, 1973; Feb 20, 1975*; Feb 21, 1975; May 19, 1975*; Feb 22, 1976 (2)
Adams: Ansel Adams Gallery (manager, Bill Turnage): Jul 06, 1973; Jul 13, 1973*; Oct 10, 1973; Oct 21, 1973; Feb 20, 1974*; Mar 19, 1974; Mar 28, 1974*; (workshop director, Norman Locks) Aug 13, 1974; Aug 25, 1974*; Oct 22, 1974*; Oct 23, 1974; Oct 30, 1974; Feb 24, 1975; Sep 01, 1975
AFRO: Aug 26, 1958*
After Dark: Jul 24, 1974
Afterimage: Jul 20, 1973
Ainsworth, Mr.: Oct 16, 1967*
Airame, Jacqueline: Jul 13, 1972; Jul 19, 1972*
Akin, Mrs.: Feb 18, 1965*
Alai, Heshmat: Mar 26, 1939
Album: Dec 12, 1969; Dec 17, 1969*; Jan 01, 1970; Feb 23, 1970; Mar 04, 1970*; Mar 11, 1970*; Mar 20, 1970*; Apr 21, 1970; Jun 24, 1970; Jul 05, 1970*; Sep 02, 1970*; Sep 07, 1970; Sep 14, 1970*; Oct 25, 1970*
Alexander, Jesse: Nov 25, 1974; Dec 03, 1974*
Alinders: Jul 22, 1968*
Allan, Fran: [Dec 24, 1972]; Dec 24, 1972*
Allen, Mary: Mar 11, 1971; Mar 26, 1971*; Aug 02, 1971; Aug 19, 1971*; Nov 02, 1971*; Nov 05, 1971
Allied Arts: Feb 03, 1974*
Alston, Elizabeth: see Look
Ameri, Victor: see Batten, Barton, Durstine & Osborn
American Academy of Arts and Sciences: May 10, 1967; Jun 18, 1967*; Mar 19, 1970; Feb 07, 1973*; Oct 15, 1974; Dec 02, 1974*; Feb 14, 1975; May 22, 1975*
American Broadcasting Company, San Francisco: Feb 12, 1965; Feb 19, 1965*
American Film Institute: Feb 19, 1971
American Foundation for the Blind, Inc.: Jan 15, 1965*; mentioned in letter dated Jan 05, 1974 from Witkin Gallery; Jan 18, 1974*; Feb 25, 1974
American Library Publishing Co.: Oct 15, 1966*
American Russian Institute: Apr 10, 1970; Apr 15, 1970*; Apr 21, 1970; Apr 27, 1970*
American Society of Magazine Photographers: Sep 18, 1958; Oct 17, 1963; Jul 14, 1965; Jul 16, 1965 (2); Sep 01, 1965; Sep 10, 1965*; Sep 14, 1965*; Sep 19, 1965*; Oct 12, 1965*; Oct 15, 1965; Nov 28, 1966*; Jan 04, 1967; also see Infinity
American West Publishing Company: May 03, 1973; May 07, 1973
American Women in the Arts: Sep 24, 1974; Oct 01, 1974*
Ampliaciones y Reproducciones Mas: Aug 02, 1968 (in Spanish); Sep 23, 1968 (in Spanish); Nov 18, 1968 (in Spanish); Nov 29, 1968 (in Spanish); Dec 22, 1968*; Jan 04, 1969 (in Spanish); Jun 06, 1969 (in Spanish); Aug 11, 1969*
Amthor Imports, Inc.: Jun 26, 1967
Anderson, Arnold: Mar 22, 1967; Mar 29, 1967*
Anderson, Michael and Karen: Oct 08, 1969 (photograph of their new baby)
Anderson, Ruth: Jan 06, 1957*
Anderson, Laura, and Polly Blank: Sep 29, 1956 (2); Dec 26, 1956*; Jan 06, 1957; Feb 08, [1957]; Feb 12, 1957*; [Jul 03, 1957]; Jul 10, 1957*; Jan 30, 1958*; Nov 17, 1959*; Mar 1966; Jan 21, 1967; Feb 04, 1967*; Feb 13, 1967; Jul 17, 1967*; Jul 26, 1968*; May 16, 1970*; Jan 01, 1972; Jun 25, 1974; Dec 18, 1974*; Apr 11, 1976*; May 31, 1976 (2); Jun 29, 1976
Andrews, Alice: see Eastman: George Eastman House
Angel Island Publications, Inc.: Jul 24, 1962; Aug 22, 1962*; Nov 19, 1962; Dec 15, 1962*
Angiulo, Anton: Jul 24, 1974 (including a photograph of Cunningham)
Anglim, Paule: Sep 30, 1974
Aperture: Jan 05, 1958; Jan 15, 1958; Feb 23, 1958; Sep 13, 1958; Dec 28, 1959; Feb 25, 1961; Feb 23, 1964; Dec 08, 1964; Dec 30, 1964*; Jan 18, 1965*; Feb 02, 1965; Mar 12, 1965*; Sep 20, 1965; Jan 17, 1966*; Feb 08, 1967; Nov 01, 1968*; Jan 16, 1970; Jan 16, 1970*; Jun 12, 1970; Dec 05, 1970; Dec 05, 1970*
Aphra: Feb 12, 1971*; Mar 11, 1971; Nov 16, 1971*; Apr 24, 1972; May 10, 1972*
Arbegast, Mai: Jul 16, 1974; Jul 18, 1974*; May 20, 1975*
Arizona State University: Feb 18, 1962; Apr 14, 1962*
Arizona: University of Arizona: Aug 06, 1975; Mar 1976; Apr 08, 1976; May 14, 1976; May 27, 1976
Armitage, Merle: Oct 1955; Aug 22, 1966*
Arnold, Mary: Dec 07, 1960*; Mar 22, 1962*
Arrow: Apr 10, 1970*; Jul 07, 1970*
Art Commission, City and County of San Francisco: see San Francisco: Art Commission
Artibus Asiae (Switzerland): Jun 03, 1958
Art Institute of Chicago: Oct 17, 1963; Nov 08, 1963*; Apr 15, 1964*; Apr 25, 1964; Apr 29, 1964; Apr 29, 1964*; May 12, 1964*; May 14, 1964; May 20, 1964*; Jul 17, 1964; Jul 21, 1964; Jul 28, 1964*; Aug 24, 1964*; Sep 23, 1964; Oct 02, 1964; Oct 17, 1964; Dec 09, 1964*
Artweek: Jun 05, 1974; Jun 07, 1974*
Asawa, Ruth: Nov 30, 1956*; Dec 24, 1959*; Sep 15, 1965; Sep 19, 1965*; Nov 27, 1971* (letter of recommendation); Mar 28, 1973*; also see San Francisco: Art Commission, City and County of San Francisco
Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies: Dec 10, 1951; Apr 22, 1952*
Association du Salon National de la Photographie: Nov 16, 1960; Nov 16, 1961
Atherton, Mrs.: Oct 29, 1967*
Atkins, Carol: see Writings
Aurelius, Vagadu and Robin: [Jan 1968]; Dec 25, 1968; Mar 13, 1971*
Austin, Sin_____ W.: Nov 02, 1967
Axvall, Lydia Strong: Jan 21, 1966*; Feb 01, 1966; Dec 22, 1968*; Mar 07, 1969; Mar 10, 1969*; Apr 16, 1969; Apr 19, 1969
B., H.: Oct 14, 1944
Baar, Betty: Oct 09, [1962]*; May 01, 1963; May 07, 1963*; Jul 09, 1963; Jul 25, 1963*; Aug 02, 1963*; Mar 31, 1964; Apr 09, 1964*; Jan 08, 1965*; Nov 02, 1974
Bacigalupi, Elkus & Salinger: Dec 02, 1959 (re Partridge vs. City and County of San Francisco); Dec 06, 1959*
Baer, Frances and Morley: Mar 07, 1965
Baer, Nancy: see American Women in the Arts
Baliken, L.: Jun 08, 1963
Ballinger, Jinny: Jul 20, 1966
Barcelon-Burger Management Corp.: Aug 01, 1975
Barchfield, Agnes and John: [Apr 11, 1976]
Barnabas, Father: see Mount Angel Abbey Library
Barnes, Marion and Eric: Nov 09, 1973
Bartlett, Lincoln: Dec 12, 1967*; Mar 31, 1970; Jun 20, 1970*; Dec 23, 1972*; Apr 15, 1973; Jun 13, 1973; Jul 09, 1973*; Dec 05, 1973*; Apr 18, 1975; Apr 08, 1976
Bathhouse Gallery: Oct 18, 1971; Jan 07, 1972 (including exhibition announcement); Feb 03, 1972; Mar 09, 1972*; Mar 10, 1972; Mar 14, 1972*; Mar 23, 1972; Mar 26, 1972; Apr 11, 1972*; Jun 09, 1972
Batten, Barton, Durstine & Osborn: Jun 21, 1967* (2); Aug 05, 1967*
Bayard, Edward: Mar 07, 1975*
Bay Area Funeral Society, Inc.: Aug 23, 1973
Bay Area Photographers: Oct 02, 1959; Oct 18, 1959*
Baylis, Douglas: Nov 28, 1971 (death announcement)
Beal, June: May 12, 1973*; Jun 23, 1973*
Beckham, Alicemarie: Mar 01, [1968]; Dec 17, [1969]
Bender: Albert M. Bender & Co., Inc.: Nov 06, 1970*
Bender: Albert M. Bender Memorial Trust: Jun 14, 1951; Mar 22, 1960; Apr 19, 1960
Benjamin, Evelyn: Jun 10, 1963
Bennett, Gordon: Jan 18, 1974
Bennett, Judith: Dec 01, 1966; Dec 12, 1966*
Benvenuto, Elio: Mar 28, 1973*; also see San Francisco: Art Commission, City and County of San Francisco
Bernstein, David: Aug 31, 1971; Sep 05, 1971*
Berriault, Gina: Nov 13, 1966; Nov 28, 1966*; Dec 05, 1966
Bertanelmer: see Hader, Berta and Elmer
Best, Signe (Mrs. Charles Best): Oct 06, 1957; Oct 08, 1974*
Bez, J. Nicholas: Feb 02, 1970; Mar 13, 1970; Nov 12, 1970*; Nov 12, 1970*; Sep 05, 1971*; also see West Coast Airlines
Bibliotheque Nationale: Oct 12, 1959*; Jun 11, 1969; Nov 08, 1969; Dec 11, 1969; Dec 29, 1969*; Jan 09, 1970; Apr 01, 1970*; Apr 28, 1970; Jul 22, 1970*; Aug 06, 1970; Jun 23, 1973; Jul 06, 1973*; Jul 28, 1973; Sep 07, 1973*; Sep 15, 1973; Oct 10, 1973*; Oct 23, 1973; Nov 03, 1973*
Biod, Karin: [Sep 1964]
Biod, Sigrid: Sep 1964
Bishop, G. Paul: Jan 14, 1971; Jan 09, 1973*
Bissantz, Betty: see Goodwin, Betty
Bissantz, Edgar and Jean: undated (5); May 30, 1948*; Mar 29, 1959; Jul 03, 1959; Nov 17, 1959; Dec 10, 1959; Dec 16, 1959*; Jan 05, 1960*; Jan 17, 1960*; Jan 21, 1960; Feb 12, 1960; Nov 21, 1960; Feb 22, 1961; Aug 05, 1961; Dec 18, 1961; May 21, 1962 (including a photograph of Joan); May 28, 1962*; Feb 05, 1963*; Feb 06, 1963*; Feb 20, 1963; Mar 20, 1963; Mar 27, 1963*; Apr 13, 1963*; Apr 25, 1963; May 14, 1963; May 27, 1963; Jun 13, 1963; Jun 17, 1963*; Jul 09, 1963*; Sep 24, 1963*; Sep 28, 1963*; Oct 26, 1963 (2); Nov 09, 1963*; Nov 20, 1963; Nov 28, 1963; Dec 01, 1963*; Dec 19, 1963; Dec 25, 1963 (photo card of Edgar); Jan 21, 1964* (including a blueprint of a house facade); Jan 27, 1964; Feb 17, 1965*; Jul 03, 1964*; Jul 19, 1964*; Sep 22, 1964*; Oct 27, 1964*; Dec 21, 1964*; Feb 01, 1965*; Feb 26, 1965; Mar 01, 1965*; Mar 14, 1965; Apr 16, 1965*; Apr 22, 1965; May 18, 1965; May 27, 1965; Jun 02, 1965*; Jun 17, 1965*; Jun 30, 1965*; Aug 14, 1965*; Aug 16, 1965; Aug 20, 1965*; Dec 08, 1965; Jan 09, 1966*; Jan 16, 1966*; Feb 28, 1966*; Mar 07, 1966*; Oct 02, 1966*; Nov 27, 1966; Jan 20, 1967; Jan 26, 1967*; [Feb 1967]*; Feb 06, 1967*; Mar 17, 1967*; Apr 16, 1967; Jun 19, 1967*; Jul 21, 1967*; Oct 10, 1967; Oct 12, 1967*; Oct 24, 1967; Oct 29, 1967*; Apr 15, 1968; Apr 22, 1968*; May 20, 1968*; Sep 12, 1968; Nov 10, 1968; Nov 21, 1968*; Dec 16, 1968; May 19, 1969; Jul 05, 1969*; Jul 21, 1969; Nov 16, 1969*; Nov 27, 1969 (including photograph); Jan 24, 1970; Aug 06, 1970*; Nov 04, 1970*; Dec 19, 1970; Jan 08, 1971*; May 16, 1971; Aug 05, 1971; Nov 02, 1971*; Nov 19, 1971*; Nov 22, 1971*; Feb 16, 1972*; Sep 06, 1972*; Jan 23, 1973; Feb 12, 1973; Apr 25, 1973*; Aug 23, 1973; Nov 13, 1973; Aug 24, 1974
Blackmarr, Philip M.: [1972] (resume)
Blank, Polly: see Andreson, Laura
Bobtoy (Chin): Aug 18, 1974
Boguszewski, Christina: Apr 04, 1949
Bookworks, The: Dec 20, 1974; Dec 28, 1974*
Boston Arts Festival: Apr 14, 1964; Aug 05, 1964
Bourke-White, Margaret: Dec 20, 1958*; Jun 24, 1971
Bourne, Frank: Sep 17, 1964*
Boyd, Collin: [Aug 23, 1974]; Aug 23, 1974*
Boyd, Nicholas: undated
Brandt, Bill: Dec 15, 1962*
Bransten, John: Jan 18, 1971; May 21, 1974*; May 31, 1974; Nov 12, 1974
Brassai family: Mar 18, 1974*
Breitenbach, Edgar and Margaret: Sep 05, 1962; Jan 11, 1963; Aug 30, 1963; Sep 07, 1963*; Sep 11, 1963; Nov 09, 1963*; Nov 18, 1963; May 25, 1965*; Jun 16, 1965; Jun 30, 1965*; May 03, 1968*; also see Library of Congress
Breitenbach, Margaret and Joseph: Dec 13, 1951; Dec 30, 1956*; Jul 19, 1958*
Breuer, Penelope: Mar 28, [1964]; May 13, 1964*; Apr 26, 1965*; May 15, 1965
Bristol, Bobbie (Horace Bristol, Jr.): Feb 09, 1957*; Feb 12, 1957; Feb 17, 1957*; Apr 09, 1958; Apr 14, 1958*; Apr 18, 1958*; Jul 10, 1958; Jan 26, 1960*; Jan 28, 1960; Jul 15, 1971*; May 27, 1972*
Bristol, Horace and Virginia: Jan 06, 1947; Nov 25, 1947; Feb 11, 1948; Feb 20, 1948; Feb 22, 1948*; Mar 11, 1948; May 03, 1948; Jun 22, 1948; Aug 14, 1948; Oct 03, 1948; Dec 06, 1949*; Dec 15, 1949; Jan 23, 1950; Jan 31, 1950*; May 17, 1950; Jun 05, 1950*; Oct 27, 1950; Nov 12, 1950*; Dec 03, 1950*; Jan 30, 1951*; Feb 08, 1951*; Mar 03, 1951; Apr 22, 1951; Sep 16, 1951*; Nov 11, 1951; Nov 24, 1951*; Jun 26, 1952*; Jul 08, 1952*; Dec 01, 1952; Aug 14, 1953; Sep 20, 1953*; Jul 11, 1956 (notification of Virginia's death); Dec 05, 1956; Dec 09, 1956*; Dec 20, 1956; Jan 08, 1957; Jan 20, 1957; Feb 26, 1957*; Mar 05, 1957 (marriage to Masako); Mar 13, 1957; Mar 19, 1957; Jun 18, 1957*; Nov 29, 1957; Dec 05, 1957*; Jul 04, 1958*; Jan 08, 1959*; Oct 13, 1959*; Sep 14, 1960; Nov 23, 1960; Nov 25, 1960*; Dec 02, 1960; Feb 21, 1961; Feb 25, 1961*; Mar 03, 1961; Mar 11, 1961*; Aug 11, 1961; Feb 23, 1962; Sep 22, 1962*; Jan 25, 1963; Mar 08, 1963*; Mar 22, 1963; May 26, 1963; Jun 12, 1963*; Jul 08, 1963; Oct 22, 1963; Dec 02, 1963; Dec 05, 1963*; Dec 12, 1963; Mar 09, 1964; Mar 27, 1964; Mar 29, 1964; Jul 03, 1964*; Sep 11, 1965*; Jan 18, 1967; Jan 24, 1967* (letter about Bristol); Apr 23, 1971*; May 03, 1971; Sep 02, 1971; Sep 08, 1971*; Mar 29, 1972*; Sep 10, 1972; Oct 01, 1972*
Britton, E. S.: Nov 16, 1947
Broadwater, Mr.: Jan 01, 1960*
Broadway High School Alumni Association: Dec 01, 1972*; Dec 09, 1972; Sep 06, 1974; Sep 08, 1974
Brooks Institute: Jun 02, 1975*
Brooks Institute Alumni Association: May 08, 1975
Brooks, Verena: Sep 28, 1974; Dec 20, 1974
Broughton, Irv: Oct 25, 1974*
Broughton, James, and Suzanna Hart: undated; Dec 08, 1952 (wedding announcement); Feb 18, 1965; Feb 14, 1969; Jun 20, 1970; Jul 25, 1970; Nov 22, 1970; Nov 26, 1970*; Dec 18, 1970* (2 receipts); [Dec 31,] 1970
Broun, Elizabeth: Jan 21, 1970; Nov 19, 1973; Nov 25, 1973*; Nov 30, 1973; Dec 05, 1973*; also see Kansas: University of Kansas
Brown, Emily: Oct 02, 1974; Oct 19, 1974*
Bruton, Esther: undated; Jan 11, 1974; Jan 17, 1974*
Bruton, Margaret and Helen: undated*; undated; Apr 09, 1970; Jan 22, 1971; Mar 21, 1971*; Jun 18, 1971*
Bry, Michael: Oct 04, 1974 (in German)
Buck, K. Robert: Sep 16, 1974; Oct 25, 1974*; Oct 30, 1974
Bullen, Reese: Apr 22, 1966; Dec 16, 1968
Bullock, Wynn and Edna: Nov 09, 1965; Nov 10, 1965*; Aug 07, 1973*; Apr 29, 1974*; May 24, 1974; Mar 23, 1976 (2); Jun 28, 1976
Bunnell, Peter: May 28, 1960; Sep 18, 1960; Oct 12, 1960*; Oct 21, 1960; Feb 13, 1961; Feb 18, 1961*; Feb 23, 1961; Aug 30, 1961; Jan 08, 1962; Feb 03, 1962; Apr 01, 1962*; Apr 09, 1962; Aug 08, 1962*; Aug 16, 1962; Sept 24, 1962; Sep 26, 1962; Nov 29, 1962; Dec 21, 1962; Jan 16, 1963; Mar 22, 1968*; Sep 29, 1968*; Jul 14, 1969*; Sep 27, 1970*; Mar 11, 1971*; also see Museum of Modern Art
Burlingame, Paul: Aug 03, 1970*; Aug 04, 1970 (with photograph); Aug 06, 1970; Aug 10, 1970*; Dec 03, 1970 (including 2 photographs); Jan 26, 1971; Mar 04, 1971; Mar 18, 1971
Burns, Robert: Jul 10, 1967*
Burstein, Beth: Mar 09, 1969*; Nov 19, 1970; Jun 24, 1976
Butler, Catherine: see Johnson, Catherine
Butler, John: undated (6); Dec 10, 1919; Nov 04, 1920 (including a photograph of Butler); Oct 05, 1946*; Oct 15, 1946; Oct 21, 1946*; Oct 24, 1946; Oct 31, 1946*; Aug 23, 1949; Mar 24, 1950; Aug 31, 1950; Oct 05, 1951*; Oct 12, 1951; Dec 14, 1951*; Jan 18, 1953; Nov 12, 1956*; Jun 21, 1957*; May 13, 1958*; Aug 03, 1958*; Dec 07, 1958*; Jan 07, 1959*; Jun 19, 1959*; Sep 23, 1959*; Jan 13, 1960; Jan 15, 1960*; Dec 19, 1960; Dec 25, 1960*; May 17, 1962*; Oct 12, 1962*; Feb 07, 1963*; Feb 19, 1963; May 08, 1963*; Dec 28, 1963*; Mar 08, 1965; Mar 08, 1965*; Jul 09, 1965*; Jul 28, 1965*; Nov 10, 1965*; Nov 09, 1966*; Dec 29, 1966*; Jul 05, 1968*; Jan 12, 1969*; Feb 03, 1969*; Mar 17, 1969; Jul 24, 1969*; Jul 05, 1970*; Aug 30, 1970*; Sep 19, 1973*
Butler, Richard and Carol: Sep 02, 1972 (wedding announcement)
Byers, Horace: Jan 10, 1929
Byron, Jim: Dec 06, 1965 (2)
C., Jack: undated
Caen, Herb: undated (2); Aug 17, 1962; Feb 02, [1964]; Aug 28, 1966*; Oct 16, 1967*; Apr 15, 1970*; May 1970; Sep 23, 1971; Jan 06, 1973*; Jan 24, 1973; also see San Francisco Chronicle
California Academy of Sciences: Apr 27, 1976; Feb 10, 1983
California Arts Commission: Feb 09, 1971 (including a booklet of clippings about a University of Santa Clara exhibition)
California Association of Women Deans and Vice-Principals: Mar 12, 1965
California College of Arts and Crafts: Nov 13, 1967; Nov 05, 1970; Nov 17, 1970*; Nov 20, 1970; Apr 23, 1971; Jun 29, 1971; Apr 07, 1972; Apr 16, 1972*; May 10, 1972; May 18, 1972; Jul 19, 1972*; Aug 22, 1972; Dec 07, 1972; Jan 1973; Jan 11, 1973; Feb 12, 1973
California Institute of the Arts: Feb 28, 1972; Mar 09, 1972*; Nov 01, 1972; Nov 07, 1972*
California League for American Indians: Mar 1961 (form letter)
California Living: Jul 05, 1972*
California Physicians' Service: Mar 16, 1966
California State University: Nov 12, 1972
California: University of California at Berkeley: Dec 11, 1956; Mar 14, 1961; Jan 05, 1962; Feb 15, 1962; May 22, 1962; May 24, 1962*; May 29, 1962; Jun 15, 1962; May 14, 1967; Jul 07, 1967; Jun 28, 1968; Jul 23, 1969; Aug 08, 1969 (2); Aug 10, 1969*; Sep 02, 1969*; Sep 04, 1969; Sep 24, 1969; Sep 24, 1969*; Sep 25, 1969; Sep 25, 1969*; Apr 24, 1970; Jul 23, 1970; Sep 07, 1972; Apr 10, 1973; Jun 01, 1973; Jun 07, 1973*; Jun 12, 1973; Jan 24, 1974; Feb 03, 1974*; Jan 27, 1976; Aug 27, 1982
California: University of California at Los Angeles: Apr 28, 1958*; May 13, 1958; May 20, 1958; Mar 09, 1960; Mar 28, 1960; Sep 07, 1960; Oct 14, 1960*; Dec 01, 1960; Apr 25, 1961; Jun 01, 1974*; Jun 21, 1974; Sep 17, 1974; Nov 20, 1974*
California: University of California at San Diego: Aug 31, 1970; Sep 14, 1970*
California: University of California at San Francisco: Apr 13, 1973* (2)
California: University of California at Santa Cruz: May 05, 1970; Aug 27, 1974
California: University of California Extension at Irvine: Nov 15, 1974; Nov 23, 1974*
California: University of California Extension at Santa Cruz: Dec 08, 1970; Dec 16, 1970*
California: University of California Extension Center, San Francisco: Jul 14, 1967*; Sep 13, 1973; Sep 15, 1973
California: University of California Press: Mar 30, 1956; Apr 20, 1956*
Call, Hughes: Jul 16, 1969*; Jul 02, 1976 (letter of condolence to Gryffyd Partridge)
Callahan, Harry: May 19, 1949
Camera: Apr 21, 1973 (letter to Witkin Gallery); Mar 07, 1974*; Jun 03, 1974*; Nov 17, 1974*; Jun 07, 1975*
Campbell, Jack: Aug 10, 1965*; Nov 27, 1971* (letter of recommendation); Jul 30, 1973; May 03, 1974*
Carr, Steve: also see Writings
Carter, William: May 01, 1975; May 20, 1975*; May 22, 1975
Case, Charles Albert: Feb 08, 1956; Feb 17, 1956; Jan 10, 1957; Jun 27, 1958; Jul 15, 1958*; Apr 04, 1959*; Feb 27, 1961*
Casebeer, Vern: Mar 04, 1971; Mar 14, 1971; Mar 26, 1971*
Casler, Chris: Jan 11, 1973
CBS News: Jun 18, 1975; Mar 30, 1976; Jun 04, 1976
Center for Creative Photography: see Arizona: University of Arizona
Center for Humanities, Inc.: Jun 05, 1974; Jun 07, 1974*
Center for Visual Studies: Jan 16, 1973*
Center of the Eye, Inc.: Mar 23, 1970; Mar 24, 1970; Jun 20, 1970*
Chaney, Verne: Dec 13, 1971; Jan 03, 1972; Feb 08, 1972*; Dec 28, 1974*